Guide to the Seattle Department of Community Development Housing and Neighborhood Development Central Files 1960-1979
Seattle Municipal Archives
- Department of Community Development Housing and Neighborhood Development Central Files, 1960-1979; 1620-02
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Rehabilitation, Standards, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 12/1)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Rehabilitation, Litigation (Hawkins) (Box-folder 12/2)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Seattle Housing, Turnkey Three, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 12/3)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Property Management, Master File, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 12/4)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Property Status, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 12/5)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, YANIP Rent Rolls, 1976 (Box-folder 12/6)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Property Maintenance, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 12/7)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Activity Reports, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 12/8)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Owners, Landlords and Tenants Liability Insurance (Box-folder 12/9)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, EMAS Study (Box-folder 12/10)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Reports, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 12/11)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Survey and Studies, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 12/12)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Physical Progress (Box-folder 12/13)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Special and Semi - Annual Reports (Box-folder 12/14)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Status of Land Acquisition, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 12/15)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Status of Land Acquisition, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 12/16)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Closeout Contract, 1977 (Box-folder 12/17)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Closeout, 1976-1977 (Box-folder 12/18)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Economic Feasibility of Land Uses in the YANIP (Report), 1973 (Box-folder 12/19)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Acquisition, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 12/20)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Request for Concurrence, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 12/21)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Appraisals (Box-folder 12/22)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Seattle Community College (Box-folder 12/23)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Citizen Participation, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 12/24)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Project Area Council, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 12/25)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Consultants, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 12/26)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Third Amendatory Loan and Grant Contract (Box-folder 12/27)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Loans and Grants, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 12/28)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Loans and Grants, 1968-1972 (Box-folder 12/29)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Correspondence, Other Departments, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 12/30)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Correspondence, General, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 13/1)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Demolition and Site Clearance, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 13/2)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Financing, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 13/3)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Non - Cash Grants - In - Aid, 1970-1977 (Box-folder 13/4)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Project Loan Notes (Box-folder 13/5)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Budgets (Box-folder 13/6)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Summary of Project Data (Box-folder 13/7)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition, General, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 13/8)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition Parcel, Number Thirteen (Box-folder 13/9)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition Parcel, Number Twenty - Three (Box-folder 13/10)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition Parcel, Number Twenty - Four (Box-folder 13/11)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Seattle Opportunities Industrialization Center, 1969-1975 (Box-folder 13/12)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Operation Breakthrough (Box-folder 13/13)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Operation Breakthrough (Box-folder 13/14)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Operation Breakthrough (Box-folder 13/15)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition Parcel, Number Twenty - Five (Box-folder 13/16)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition Parcel, Number Twenty - Six (Box-folder 13/17)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition Parcel, (Daycare) Number Twenty - Six (Box-folder 13/18)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition Parcel, Number Thirty - One (Box-folder 13/19)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition Parcel, Number Forty - Nine A (Box-folder 13/20)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition Parcel, Number Fifty - Three A (Box-folder 13/21)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition Parcel, Number Seventy - Eight (Box-folder 13/22)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, High Rise for the Elderly (Box-folder 13/23)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition Parcel, Number Twenty - Four B (Box-folder 13/24)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition Parcel, Number Nineteen and Twenty (Box-folder 13/25)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition Parcel, Number Twenty - Nine A (Box-folder 13/26)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Disposition Parcel, Number Forty and Forty - One (Box-folder 13/27)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, CETS verses Hawkins, USA (Box-folder 14/1)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Edwards, and Others verses City Council (Box-folder 14/2)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, J. Dalton P and H Verses Erna Backman (Box-folder 14/3)
  - Yesler / Atlantic, Shopping Center Site (Box-folder 14/4)
  - Leschi, Rehabilitation, General, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 14/5)
  - Leschi, Rehabilitation, General, 1975-1976 (Box-folder 14/6)
  - Leschi, Rehabilitation, General, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 14/7)
  - Leschi, Rehabilitation, General, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 14/8)
  - Leschi, Rehabilitation, Berry - Pounds, 1969-1976 (Box-folder 14/9)
  - Leschi, Rehabilitation, Agreement, Building Department (Box-folder 14/10)
  - Leschi, Rehabilitation, FHA Inspection (Box-folder 14/11)
  - North Greenwood, Housing Rehabilitation, 1969-1977 (Box-folder 14/12)
  - North Greenwood, Rehabilitation, General (Box-folder 14/13)
  - North Greenwood, Rehabilitation, General (Box-folder 14/14)
  - North Greenwood, Rehabilitation, General (Box-folder 14/15)
  - North Greenwood, Rehabilitation, General (Box-folder 15/1)
  - South Park, Rehabilitation, General (Box-folder 15/2)
  - South Park, Rehabilitation, General (Box-folder 15/3)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Relocation General, 1974-1977 (Box-folder 15/4)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Relocation and Property Management, Relocation - Code Enforcement (Box-folder 15/5)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Minority Housing (Box-folder 15/6)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Relocation Housing Resources General (Box-folder 15/7)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Multi - Family Housing (Box-folder 15/8)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Relocation, FACE Program (Box-folder 15/9)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Rehabilitation, 312 Loans, 1975 (Box-folder 15/10)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Rehabilitation, General, 1962-1973 (Box-folder 15/11)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Rehabilitation, 312 Loans, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 15/12)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Rehabilitation, 312 Loans, 1970-1973 (Box-folder 15/13)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Rehabilitation, General, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 15/14)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Rehabilitation, General, 1974 (Box-folder 15/15)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Project Improvements, General (Box-folder 16/1)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Project Improvements, CIP (Box-folder 16/2)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Model Cities, Other Departments (Box-folder 16/3)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Relocation General, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 16/4)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Relocation General, 1963-1973 (Box-folder 16/5)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Relocation, 221 (d) (3) Housing (Box-folder 16/6)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Property Management Income Expenditures (Box-folder 16/7)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Relocation, Appeal Procedures (Box-folder 16/8)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Correspondence, General, 1974 (Box-folder 16/9)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Administrative Policies and Decisions (Mayor) (Box-folder 16/10)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Correspondence, General, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 16/11)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Correspondence, General, 1962-1970 (Box-folder 16/12)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Correspondence, City Officials, 1960-1964 (Box-folder 16/13)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Mission Statements (Box-folder 16/14)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Audits, Office of Management and Budget (Box-folder 16/15)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Reports and Studies, Seattle Development Program (Box-folder 16/16)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Reports and Studies, HUD Annual Report on Real Estate Acquisition. (Box-folder 16/17)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Reports and Studies, Management Study (Touche - Ross), 1972 (Box-folder 16/18)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Overview (Box-folder 16/19)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Reports and Studies, Workable Program (Box-folder 16/20)
  - Housing and Neighborhood Development, Mission Statements, General (Box-folder 16/21)
  - Activity Reports, 1977-1979 (Box-folder 17/1)
  - Activity Reports, Weekly - Engineering Coordinator, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 17/2)
  - Activity Reports, Weekly - Engineering Coordinator, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 17/3)
  - Activity Reports, Weekly - Architectural Supervisor, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 17/4)
  - Demolition - Environmental Impact, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 17/5)
  - Demolition Procedure, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 17/6)
  - Demolition Projections, 1972-1975 (Box-folder 17/7)
  - Langston Hughes Cultural Center, 1973 (Box-folder 17/8)
  - Leschi Acquisitions, undated (Box-folder 17/9)
  - Leschi Demolitions (Includes Photographs), 1972-1976 (Box-folder 17/10)
  - Leschi Demolitions (Includes Photographs), 1972-1974 (Box-folder 17/11)
  - Leschi NW Phase B, 1971-1975 (Box-folder 17/12)
  - Leschi, Southwest Street Tree Planting, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 17/13)
  - NCGIA Projects, 1973 (Box-folder 17/14)
  - North Greenwood Demolitions, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 18/1)
  - North Greenwood Property Rehab Standards, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 18/2)
  - North Greenwood Storm Drains, Contract No. 2, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 18/3)
  - North Greenwood Storm Drains, Contract No. 3, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 18/4)
  - Northlake Demolitions, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 18/5)
  - Pike Project Demolition - Baker Building, 1975 (Box-folder 18/6)
  - Pike Project Demolition - Bayview Hotel, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 18/7)
  - Pike Project Demolition - Billboards, 1974 (Box-folder 18/8)
  - Pike Project Demolition - Municipal Market Building, 1974 (Box-folder 18/9)
  - Pike Project Demolition - Future, 1974 (Box-folder 18/10)
  - Pike Plaza Historical Survey (Incl. Photographs), 1971 (Box-folder 18/11)
  - Pike Plaza - Rehab Standards, 1972 (Box-folder 18/12)
  - Pike Project Sanitary and Storm Drain, 1968-1975 (Box-folder 18/13)
  - Pike Plaza Shore Land Management, 1973 (Box-folder 18/14)
  - Pike Project Soil Tests, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 18/15)
  - Pike Project - Street Vacation Drawings, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 19/1)
  - Pike Project - Street Vacations, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 19/2)
  - Pike Project - Study and Re-evaluation of Public Improvements, 1974 (Box-folder 19/3)
  - Pike Project - Study and Re-evaluation of Public Improvements, 1967-1973 (Box-folder 19/4)
  - Pike Plaza Temporary Park, 1972 (Box-folder 19/5)
  - Pike Project - Undergrounding, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 19/6)
  - Pike Project - Union St. Stairway, 1972 (Box-folder 19/7)
  - Pike Place View Site, 1971 (Box-folder 19/8)
  - Proposed Development Evaluation Guidelines, undated (Box-folder 19/9)
  - Quarterly Work Programs, 1973-1975 (Box-folder 19/10)
  - South Park Demolitions, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 19/11)
  - South Park General, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 19/12)
  - South Park NDP General Correspondence (Incl Photographs), 1971-1973 (Box-folder 19/13)
  - South Park NDP, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 19/14)
  - South Seattle Redevelopment Project, 1966-1973 (Box-folder 20/1)
  - Yesler - Atlantic - 20th Ave S. et al Widening (Incl Photographs), 1975-1976 (Box-folder 20/2)
  - Yesler - Atlantic - 20th Ave S. et al Widening, 1975 (Box-folder 20/3)
  - Yesler - Atlantic - 20th Ave S. et al Widening, 1973-1974 (Box-folder 20/4)
  - Yesler - Atlantic Acquisitions, undated (Box-folder 20/5)
  - Yesler - Atlantic, Alley Block 22, Hill Track Add, 1974-1976 (Box-folder 20/6)
  - Yesler - Atlantic Closeout, 1977 (Box-folder 20/7)
  - Yesler - Atlantic Demolitions (Incl Photographs), 1972-1976 (Box-folder 20/8)
  - Yesler - Atlantic Demolitions, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 20/9)
  - Yesler - Atlantic EIS, 1974 (Box-folder 20/10)
  - Yesler - Atlantic Garfield B Backup, 1972 (Box-folder 20/11)
  - Yesler - Atlantic Land Surveys, 1973 (Box-folder 20/12)
  - Yesler - Atlantic, Operation Breakthrough, Electrical, 1970-1972 (Box-folder 20/13)
  - Yesler - Atlantic Park and Recreation Facility, 1971-1973 (Box-folder 20/14)
  - Yesler - Atlantic Pedestrian Pathway, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 20/15)
  - Yesler - Atlantic, S. Main St. et al Widening, 1971-1972 (Box-folder 21/1)
  - Yesler - Atlantic, S. Main St. et al Widening, Drawings, 1971 (Box-folder 21/2)
  - Yesler - Atlantic, S. Main St. et al Widening, Landscape Drawings, 1972 (Box-folder 21/3)
  - Yesler - Atlantic, S. Washington St. et al Widening, 1975-1977 (Box-folder 21/4)
  - Yesler - Atlantic, S. Washington St. et al Widening, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 21/5)
  - Yesler - Atlantic, S. Washington St. et al Widening, 1972-1974 (Box-folder 21/6)
  - Yesler - Atlantic Street Vacation Status Report, 1974-1975 (Box-folder 21/7)
  - Yesler - Atlantic, Wonder Bread Bakery, 1972-1973 (Box-folder 21/8)